但是我们需要等一会才能测试我们的代码  我们仍然需要
But it will be a while before we can test this in our code. We still are going
实现很多的代码  包括UI界面
to implement a whole layer on top of it along with a bunch of UI changes.
幸运的是  我们可以让JUnit测试帮助我们完成这些  大家仔细看
Fortunately, we can implement JUnit test here to help. And now for
我的操作  我们先在Android Studio工程的src文件夹下创建一个
some magic. We'll add a directory to the source directory of our Android Studio
androidTest文件夹  然后在它的下面再继续创建一个java文件夹
project called androidTest. And then, another one underneath it called java.
这样Android Studio就知道我们有一个针对App的测试
This is the way we tell Android Studio there's a test target in gradle for
现在我们创建一个测试包  这个测试包的包名是主包名后面
our App. Now we create a test package that matches our main package with
再加上test后缀  在这个测试包中创建一个新的
an extra test directory on the end. Create a new class called
叫fullTestSuite的类  添加上这些代码
fullTestSuite in the test package. Add this code. This
这是一些可以让我们将其它类添加到测试中的模板代码
is some boiler plate code that will allow us to add tests in additional classes.
下面我们来创建一个继承自AndroidTestCase的TestDb类
Next, we'll create a TestDb class that extends AndroidTestCase [NOISE] and
添加一个创建数据库的测试  可以这样进行测试是因为TestRunner会
add a test that creates our Db. The way this works is that the TestRunner
按照定义的顺序执行这个类中的
will execute every function in our class that begins with test in the order that
以test开头的方法  每个测试都需要有一种导致断言失败
they are declared in the class. Each test should have a failure path that
的情况  在进行测试之前我们先删除数据库  这样
uses an assert. We start by deleting the database before testing it. So,
我们可以进行简洁的测试  我们先到运行app的下拉菜单中来启动测试
we have a clean test. Now, to run the test we go to the app start drop down.
选择编辑配置  再选择添加来添加一个新的配置
And select Edit Configurations. We select Plus to add a new configuration. And
选择针对App模块的Android Tests  并对它进行命名
select Android Tests Against Module App. Now we name the test.
注意一下这里默认是运行模拟器的  所以
Now note that it tends to target the emulator by default. So,
要使用真实的设备的话我们要选择显示选择对话框的选项
I want to use an actual device I'm going to select Show Chooser Dialogue.
现在我们就可以在我们的设备上进行测试了  这里显示测试通过了
Now we can just run the test against our device. And, it passes. So
我们再来进行一下数据库的插入和读取测试  作为开始
let's create a database insert and read test. At the beginning of it,
我们向每一个表中插入一行数据  我们先使用一些虚拟的
we'll insert a single record into each table. We'll begin with some dummy
位置信息  我们使用dbHelper对象获取一个可写数据库实例
data for our location. We'll use the dbHelper to get a writeable database.
这就是我们之前在项目中设计的使用数据库的方式
This is exactly how we will use the database when we code it up in our project.
然后创建一个ContentValues对象  它在Android中可以用来方便地
We'll then create a ContentValues object, which is a handy helper object that
存储键值对  我们会把这些虚拟数据存入
Android uses to store values and keys. We'll store our dummy data into
LocationEntry类中定义的对应列中  注意到为了直接通过类名
the columns from our LocationEntry contract. Note that in order to make it
进行编码  我在这里做了一些额外的导入包中的类的操作
work with this abbreviated syntax, I did have to add some extra imports up here.
然后我们把数据插入数据库  并验证插入这一行数据成功了
We then insert the data into our database, and verified that we got a row back.
我发现在测试类中打印一些log信息是非常有用的
Now I find that it's helpful to put log messages into my test cases.
现在我们再用数据库的读操作从数据库中读取出我们之前存入的
Now we'll use the database read operations to pull our dummy data back out of
虚拟数据  我们在这里使用一个自定义的映射  理论上讲
the database. We're making use of a custom projection here which, in theory,
这会使我们更方便地查找我们需要的数据集
would make it easy to use our database cursor to query for the values we want.
虽然我们用了自定义的映射  但是它并不是必须的
We use a custom projection here. Although, it's not required.
如果不使用自定义映射  那么会返回包含所有列的数据集
If the custom projection wasn't there, we would simply return all columns.
一个数据库游标是用来对数据库中的数据集进行遍历操作的
A database cursor is a control structure that enables traversal over
控制结构  在Android中  这是用一个Cursor对象来表示的
the records in a database. In Android, this is represented by a Cursor object.
Cursor对象可以让我们在查询的结果集中进行遍历操作
The Cursor object allows one to traverse between records in a query and
也可以获取结果集中的任意数据项
get the contents of any individual column from a query.
现在  我们使用cursor.moveToFirst()方法来以行为单位对cursor对象进行操作
Now, we use cursor.moveToFirst() to populate our cursor with our row of data.
然后可以再通过每列的索引获取数据项  最后
We can then pull out our data by index. Finally assert
对这些数据和之前的虚拟数据是否一样进行断言  现在再运行一下我们的测试
if it doesn't match our dummy data. And now, we get to run our tests again.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
这里显示测试通过了
And they passed.